thefrankmedrano.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Frank Medrano

## FRANKMEDRANO.COM INC. PRIVACY POLICY

FrankMedrano.com Inc. (“ **Frank Medrano** ”) is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the integrity of any identifiable information that is collected about you (your " **Personal Information** ") through the www.FrankMedrano.com website and any related websites of Frank Medrano’s (collectively, the “ **Site** ”). Frank Medrano believes that it is important that the Site users understand what Personal Information is collected and the following Privacy Policy explains Frank Medrano’s privacy practices, describes the steps that Frank Medrano takes to keep your Personal Information confidential, to inform you about how and why Frank Medrano collects Personal Information and to provide you with Frank Medrano’s contact information should you have questions or concerns about our online Personal Information protection practices. We understand that you want control over how Frank Medrano collects, uses and discloses your Personal Information.

**What type of Personal Information does Frank Medrano collect?**

Frank Medrano may collect Personal Information from you when you voluntarily provide it to us through a number of features available on the Site. For example, we may ask you to provide personal information if you:

  * Register to subscribe for free recipes, fasting tutorials, daily workouts, or other free email subscription service;
  * Register for the free mobile application;
  * Ask to receive online information from us;
  * Register for a contest, free giveaways, or other promotion;
  * Register to leave a comment or testimonial about Frank Medrano's products;
  * Participate in a review, survey, customer research panel, or similar type of activity; and/or
  * Otherwise participate in features of our website that ask for Personal Information.

In addition, if you purchase or otherwise request a product, publication, or promotional offering from us you may be required to provide your contact and/or payment information (such as a credit card number) in order for us to process your request.

Frank Medrano may also collect your Personal Information through clickstreaming (a technology that allows the Site to track the paths that you take as you access the Site, and as you use links to other sites), web beacons (small, graphic images that allows the Site to collect certain information and monitor user activity), and Site traffic information – Frank Medrano monitors and analyses traffic information on the Site in order to determine which features and services are popular and useful to visitors, so that Frank Medrano can improve our services.

Lastly, our Site also seeks (as many websites do) to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer's hard drive which allows the Site's server to identify the computer when it visits again, in order to improve Site navigation. This cookie is not used to obtain Personal Information, and the information that is tracked is used for internal purposes only. However, if you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your web browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed.

**How we use your Personal Information**  
Your participation in any of these activities is voluntary and we will only use the personal information you provide for the purposes for which it was collected. For example, we may use the Personal Information we collect to: respond to your questions or comments; administer our promotions and the Site; fulfill your request, subscription or order; and/or otherwise provide or improve our products and services. We will not send you any online newsletters or similar email communications unless you expressly consent to receive such a communication from us. We may, however, send you notices of changes to our Privacy Policy.

You may be given the opportunity to consent to receive future promotional communications from us. If you opt-in to receive such communications, we may use the information to: communicate with you regarding our products, services and promotions; provide you with other information you request; and/or improve our product and service offerings. You will always have the opportunity to “unsubscribe” from receiving communications at any time.

**How does Frank Medrano collect Personal Information?**  
Frank Medrano will only collect Personal Information that you have voluntarily provided to us. Frank Medrano will not collect any Personal Information about you without informing you ahead of time, either through this Privacy Policy or at the time Frank Medrano is requesting Personal Information from you, why and how Personal Information is being collected and how such Personal Information will be used or disclosed (if applicable).

**How Frank Medrano protects your Personal Information**  
Frank Medrano keeps your Personal Information and the business that you do with us in strict confidence. You have control over how Frank Medrano obtains, uses, and gives out information about you. You also have access to the information that Frank Medrano has about you and Frank Medrano respects your privacy when we market our products and services.

**How Frank Medrano may share or disclose Personal Information**  
Frank Medrano does not sell to third parties any Personal Information that Frank Medrano collects. Frank Medrano may provide or share the Personal Information that you provide with third parties or promotional partners who provide services on our behalf. These entities may use the information solely in conjunction with the specific services they provide to us (e.g. fulfillment of an order; responding to your question or comment; providing a promotional prize; deployment of a consumer survey; and/or investigation of a complaint).

Frank Medrano may collect, use or disclose information without your consent if Frank Medrano: i) must disclose information for legal reasons; (ii) has to protect the interests of Frank Medrano, for example, to detect or prevent fraud; iii) must use an outside company to process information - at times Frank Medrano may use the expertise of an outside company to do work for us involving some of your Personal Information. When Frank Medrano does use an outside company, we select the company carefully and confirm that it uses security and privacy standards comparable to those of Frank Medrano.

Personal Information may be subject to transfer to another organization. This might occur, for example, in contemplation of a merger or a change of ownership of all or part of Frank Medrano. Frank Medrano will do this only if the parties have entered into an agreement under which the disclosure of the information (including any Personal Information) is restricted to those purposes that relate to the business transaction and is to be used by the parties to carry out and complete the business transaction.

**Consent to use of Personal Information**  
By choosing to provide Frank Medrano with your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy, you are further consenting to its use in accordance with the principles outlined in this Privacy Policy and as may be further outlined at the time of collection. Frank Medrano will rely upon such implied consent to use and disclose identifying information about you, such as your name and address.

The protection of your Personal Information is of critical importance to us. If you don't want Frank Medrano to use Personal Information for marketing or publicity purposes, please tell us at the time the information is collected. You may withdraw your consent any time after you have given it to us, provided there are no legal requirements to prevent this, by sending an e-mail to support@FrankMedrano.com.

Please note, if you do not consent to certain uses of information, or if you withdraw your consent, Frank Medrano may not be able to provide you with a particular product or service. If so, Frank Medrano will explain the situation to you to help you with your decision.

**Requests for access or correction of Personal Information**  
Requests to access or correct any Personal Information held about you may be submitted in writing to the address listed at “Contact Information,” below. After we have verified your identity, we will endeavor to provide the information requested within the time specified by local law or within a reasonable period of time. If your information is shown to be inaccurate, we will endeavor to correct it as appropriate. If we decline to provide the Personal Information held or to make the correction requested, we will provide reasons for such decline.  
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to deal quickly with your request to see your information, and always respond to you within thirty (30) days. If Frank Medrano needs to extend the time, or Frank Medrano has to refuse your request, Frank Medrano will tell you why, subject to any legal restrictions and will notify you of the new deadline, the reasons for the extension, and your rights under applicable legislation respecting the extension.

**Security**

Frank Medrano takes reasonable and appropriate measures to keep Personal Information accurate and up-to-date. In an effort to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of Personal Information, Frank Medrano takes appropriate physical, organizational and technical measures to protect Personal Information.  
However, for greater clarity, Frank Medrano cannot guarantee that any information that you may choose to disclose via the Internet will not be intercepted by third parties. We assume no responsibility for Personal Information disclosed through the Internet, which is intercepted, diverted or otherwise accessed.

Personal Information collected by Frank Medrano may be stored at locations outside of the United States and as such is subject to the law of such other jurisdictions. Personal Information may be accessed by foreign governments or law enforcement in such other jurisdictions and Frank Medrano may be required to disclose such Personal Information by operation of law.

**Retention and disposal of Personal Information**  
Frank Medrano keeps your Personal Information only so long as we need it for the products and services that you are using, to offer you products and services when you are a customer and for a reasonable time thereafter, or to meet any legal requirements. Frank Medrano destroys your Personal Information when it is no longer needed, or we remove your name from the Personal Information.

**Consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy**

By using the Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you signify assent to all of the terms of this Privacy Policy and our [Terms and Conditions.](http://www.frankmedrano.com/terms-of-service/) If you do not agree with any terms of this Privacy Policy or our [Terms and Conditions and Disclaimer](http://www.frankmedrano.com/terms-of-service/), please do not use the Site or submit any Personal Information to us.

This Privacy Policy may be modified as a result of amendments to the law or due to other reasons. We will not materially change the purposes for which we collect or disclose your Personal Information without first obtaining your consent.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or complaints about our Privacy Policy, please let us know right away by sending the Chief Privacy Officer an email at support@FrankMedrano.com.
